<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home on Gus Reid|Move True</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home on Gus Reid|Move True</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Breakthroughs and Intention</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/breakthroughs-and-intention/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/breakthroughs-and-intention/</guid>
      <description>Picture this, you go on retreat and you have a breakthrough. Maybe you get to the root of a habit that you formulated in reaction to a traumatic event in your childhood, or you had a direct experience of an existential distinction or principle, like groundedness or space. And you feel amazing - you&amp;rsquo;re rooted in your feeling-awareness and you feel free and light. Your body, mind and being are more effectively aligned to the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Paths - Distraction or Obstacle</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/two-paths---distraction-or-obstacle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/two-paths---distraction-or-obstacle/</guid>
      <description>This shit scares me. I&amp;rsquo;m afraid to write in public. I&amp;rsquo;m afraid to share what I see, partly because what I see goes in stark contrast to the prevailing winds, and partly because I&amp;rsquo;m afraid to reveal to the world my inner-most truths.&#xA;But I write anyway because I see that there are only two paths for me in life:&#xA;The path of the next distraction, or The path of the next obstacle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hold On to Let Go</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/hold-on-to-let-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/hold-on-to-let-go/</guid>
      <description>Introduction One of the best things we can do for our health, life and relationships is to train the mind. And one of the most beneficial things we can train the mind to do is let go.&#xA;Relaxation Relaxation is the precursor to anything effective in this life. Whether it&#39;s communicating, playing a sport or being creative; adopting a relaxed state is going to bring about more desirable results than if we&#39;re tense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugs: Who Needs Them?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/drugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/drugs/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a spontaneous bit about MDMA and weed:&#xA;Enjoy, Gus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting High on Your Own Supply</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/getting-high-on-your-own-supply/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/getting-high-on-your-own-supply/</guid>
      <description>Psychedelics A path to higher consciousness or a potential trap? Having participated in several dozen ayahuasca, huyachuma and mushroom ceremonies - even going through intense training with the Shipibo tribe of the Amazon to become a curandero. Having had hundreds of &amp;ldquo;less formal&amp;rdquo; experiences with LSD, mushrooms and various other natural and synthetic psychedelics, from age 13, right up until my mid-forties. And, contrasting the results of all those experiences with those of the internal and external arts, and contemplative practices I&amp;rsquo;ve been committed to over the last 13 years, I would like to share some perspective on my observations of the usefulness and sustainability of psychedelic-use for the purpose of transformation - or, what I call, living lucidly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering the Body to Master Life</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/mastering-the-body-to-master-life1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/mastering-the-body-to-master-life1/</guid>
      <description>Mastering the Body to Master Life As a culture we tend to have two primary identification-points; that of being a body, and that of being an mind. We hold it that the mind is dependant on the body for its existence, and yet we award the mind great authority in our lives. The journey towards becoming authentic and lucid in our lives could be simply stated as one of surrendering the mind to the body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi,&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m Gus and I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about movement; not only as a therapeutic tool, but as vehicle for inner transformation.&#xA;I was born in the most unlikely of places - Oklahoma City, USA. At age seven I moved to the UK, where I picked up a healthy dose of British conditioning, which (sorry Okies), I&amp;rsquo;m (mostly) grateful for. I have spent a healthy chunk of my adult life traveling and experiencing different cultures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/classes/</guid>
      <description>Online Classes: Class Link&#xA;What&amp;rsquo;s possible when we live our lives from a state of relaxed, open, grounded awareness; meeting life centred in our being, whole and complete?&#xA;My classes are aimed at creating the conditions that give your body experiences that are in harmony with your true nature; to provide an experiential contrast to the habits of the conditioned mind; opening up the possibility of new and improved experiences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work with Me</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/work-with-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/work-with-me/</guid>
      <description>1-to-1 Sessions and Individualised Programmes: My goal is to help you live a lucid and empowered life through releasing attachment to mind-identification and allowing yourself to just be. There are two domains of study I am equipped to support you with in this pursuit:&#xA;Cultivating awareness through the body, and Ontological investigation These two domains of study work hand-in-hand, and students that study both have the best results.&#xA;Cultivating awareness through the body: It&amp;rsquo;s my experience that the mind and body are inextricably linked.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
