<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Movement: Unleashed</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Movement: Unleashed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Myth of Instant Enlightenment</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/the-myth-of-instant-enlightenment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/the-myth-of-instant-enlightenment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;events-and-process&#34;&gt;Events and Process&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve all been there…&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We went to a plant ceremony, breathwork session, meditation retreat or just learned something new that opened us to something we hadn’t seen before.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We feel open, expansive - invincible!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We think things will never be the same and we are full of the joy of life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then hours, days or weeks later it fades and we find ourselves in the same old reactive patterns and habits.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakthroughs and Intention</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/breakthroughs-and-intention/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/breakthroughs-and-intention/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;willpower-or-intent&#34;&gt;Willpower or Intent?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Picture this, you go on retreat and you have a breakthrough. Maybe you get to the root of a habit that you formulated in reaction to a traumatic event in your childhood, or you had a direct experience of an existential distinction or principle, like groundedness or space. And you feel amazing - you&amp;rsquo;re rooted in your feeling-awareness - you feel free and light. Your body, mind and being are more effectively aligned to the world. Tension runs off you like water off a duck&amp;rsquo;s back.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Paths - Distraction or Obstacle</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/two-paths---distraction-or-obstacle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/two-paths---distraction-or-obstacle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This shit scares me. I&amp;rsquo;m afraid to write in public. I&amp;rsquo;m afraid to share what I see, partly because what I see goes in stark contrast to the prevailing winds, and partly because I&amp;rsquo;m afraid to reveal to the world my inner-most truths.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But I write anyway because I see that there are only two paths for me in life:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The path of the next distraction, or&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The path of the next obstacle.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I sit down to write and all I&amp;rsquo;m faced with is a blank screen my whole body and being is filled with terror.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hold On to Let Go</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/hold-on-to-let-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/hold-on-to-let-go/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the best things we can do for our health, life and relationships is to train the mind. And one of the most beneficial things we can train the mind to do is let go.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;relaxation&#34;&gt;Relaxation&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;article__head&#34; style=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/holdonletgo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; height=&#34;250px&#34; width=&#34;250px&#34; style=&#34;float: right; margin-left: 15px;&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;Relaxation is the precursor to anything effective in this life. Whether it&#39;s communicating, playing a sport or being creative; adopting a relaxed state is going to bring about more desirable results than if we&#39;re tense. And letting go is the precursor to relaxation. &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But why are we so tense? There are countless reasons why we hold unconscious tension in our bodies. From old injuries and resulting bracing and compensatory habits; to mental and emotional dispositions, based on core assumptions about self, others, and life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugs: Who Needs Them?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/drugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/drugs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a spontaneous bit about MDMA and weed:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vI2VBKhfU9s?si=Bn7X5CIp5AKdPbXx&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enjoy,&#xA;Gus&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting High on Your Own Supply</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/getting-high-on-your-own-supply/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/getting-high-on-your-own-supply/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h5 id=&#34;psychedelics&#34;&gt;Psychedelics&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;h6 id=&#34;a-path-to-higher-consciousness-or-a-potential-trap&#34;&gt;A path to higher consciousness or a potential trap?&lt;/h6&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Having participated in several dozen ayahuasca, huyachuma and mushroom ceremonies - even going through intense training with the Shipibo tribe of the Amazon to become a curandero. Having had hundreds of &amp;ldquo;less formal&amp;rdquo; experiences with LSD, mushrooms and various other natural and synthetic psychedelics, from age 13, right up until my mid-forties. And, contrasting the results of all those experiences with those of the internal and external arts, and contemplative practices I&amp;rsquo;ve been committed to over the last 13 years, I would like to share some perspective on my observations of the usefulness and sustainability of psychedelic-use for the purpose of transformation - or, what I call, living lucidly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering the Body to Master Life</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/mastering-the-body-to-master-life1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/mastering-the-body-to-master-life1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;mastering-the-body-to-master-life&#34;&gt;Mastering the Body to Master Life&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a culture we tend to have two primary identification-points; that of being a body, and that of being an mind. We hold it that the mind is dependant on the body for its existence, and yet we award the mind great authority in our lives. The journey towards becoming authentic and lucid in our lives could be simply stated as  one of surrendering the mind to the body.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
